# Riyan Naffa Nusafara







## SUMMARY

I am an Information Engineering undergraduate student, Faculty of Engineering of Universitas Gadjah Mada. My fields of expertise are analytical mathematics, data analytics, and mathematical programming. I am currently learning image processing and website development.

# Work Experience

### Majelis Permusyawaratan Mahasiswa KMFT UGM

April 2024 - present

In position of the II Comission, with responsibilities of supervising and handling financial audits of Semi-Autonomous Bodies of Keluarga Mahasiswa Fakultas Teknik Universitas Gadjah Mada.

## FindIT! Informatics Competition Committee

Nov 2023 - May 2024

In charge of problem-setting, external communication, and competition supervising.

#### Smansa Edu Fair Committee

Nov 2023 - Jan 2024

In charge of the External Affairs division.

Enforian Sep 2023 - Nov 2023

In charge of acting.

#### Freelance Course Instructor

Jan 2023 - present

- Course Instructor of Mathematics and Programming.
- Mathematics and Programming Instructor for Informatics Competition.

## EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree at Universitas Gadjah Mada 2023 - present

2020 - 2023 SMA Negeri 1 Majenang (Best Math-Sci Graduating Student)

## ACHIEVEMENTS

1st Winner of Cilacap Regional Informatics Olympiad (Best Math-Sci Graduating Student)

# SKILLS

Programming Image Processing, Web Development, Data Analysis

Languages/Tools C++, Python, Rust, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jupyter Notebook, LATEX

Last updated: May 20, 2024